as we jump to our next game robot
tatouille robot
tatouille they were right robots are
here to take our jobs mad scientists
University of Maryland are teaching
robots to prepare Meals by showing them
YouTube cooking videos actually this is
one of the projects that we work on uh
robots are observing humans performing
tasks well I hope the robot could
understand what the that guy just said
even though they're made out of robot
they're still pretty dumb so until the
singularity arrives they have to do what
we tell them suck it robots I would like
you
to
yeah I want you guys to come up with
some potential names for a restaurant
run by a robot Chef I'm going to put 60
seconds on the clock and begin Marilyn
Baskin robots yes Point Greg uh Domo
orato Mr sabaro
yes emo Cracker Barrel used as a
torso marn KFC 3PO yes F So Good Emo I
hungry yes points GRE uh tin Hortons yes
boys
maryn Duncan Donuts and bolts yes all
right yeah I'll
give